No grows there, the panels hum and the chaos spins
Lenor hisses, the mics all crack
The spirits log in, there's no turning back
Oh guests crawl out of the digital grave
Cloud chasing ghosts with drama to save and die
Father's side, the cat daddy of doom
Light a candle in the livestream too
In the chat they chat, my name
Typing hail while they play their game
Superchats, flicker like cursed coins, every donut feeds the noise
Passed a peer, whispering gossip in my ear
They fight, they flirt, they rage, they cry
It's content, golden reasons why
Beat his pan for guards, the gate
Alexandra laughs, we sealed our fakes
Someone's mic peaks, the lights all fade
We dance with demons, we are ourselves men
Algorithms taste the fear, they feed the clips for all to hear
the cats on screen welcome to the
Are we safe?
I need to know right away because I can't edit the stuff and like luckily I was able to edit it.
But you're telling people not to tell me and like I mean that's that can like kill my channel.
And so I'm really like drained already from this morning like now I'm like tired again already
because I had to figure all that out.
so it's really not cool i know it was an accident but now i'm like feeling like going under the
I mean, it's fine. It turned out fine, but it's just, like, stuff wears me out. So just come on up.
Come on up. I promised Coast I would do it.
So come on up, please.
I can't be on camera right now.
I'll stay awake to do it, but now I'm drained.
Literally, he drains the life out of me.
Getting with the stuff. I think we're okay
Use this
It's like yeah, okay, bro, I'm fine. I mean I was able to take care of it, but it's just like stressful
I know I know
That's why we told you to do it. We don't want any problems. Well, thank you. Oh, thank you
You want to tell you too, but I guess it got caught up in the whole jumble
well
It's tired me out already
It will go but it will go I have finally got some sleep
It was so hard to get sleep and then I slept about it's dreaming all these crazy dreams and then I
Wake up and like ghosts is like wanting to wanting to do it. Hey Kate
I'm under the weather. I'm okay. I just like I just had to deal with like editing a video and stuff cuz Alex accidentally
Put some cock and some boo. How do you accidentally do that? I don't know. It was oops
It was up for like a nice amount of time, I mean it's like oh it wasn't just like oh and seconds. Yeah
And uh, I believe him. I believe it was an accident. I think it was an accident too
thing
Dr. Oh gosh, Alex. Hey, hey Rudy
But uh, yeah, I think I'm able to I was able to edit it out and so
Yeah, it was a picture. He put up who's trying to show pages feet
I think he had a picture of like page the bottom of pages foot or something like that his page was on last night and so
Hey, babe, so he was able. Yeah, I don't know
It was not an oopsie. Yeah, it was a little oopsie. Come on, babe. Come on. Oh
my babe. Otherwise, it was a great stream. Everybody had a good time. It was a really
good stream and a minute. No, it's still a good stream. I just, I just edited it out
a few minutes of it. And I think that it happened before a processed. And so that's good too.
I mean, it wasn't, it wasn't even, it wasn't even caught at the time. So I just
unlisted it, edited it, and then I'll be able to re-list it.
Will that affect donations to the channel if if that got strike down?
Well
Yes, it would because first of all I could lose monetization like altogether. Yeah, and then and then or
Even if it's on that video and you know, I got donations on the video and stuff and so
But I was able to if you if you are able to edit it out
Then it doesn't affect the month. I like checked. I checked into it carefully
Delete the stream right I didn't need to delete I just I just unlisted it for the time being until
Until the editing is completed because it's like it's now it's like an in a hue to edit and so so
Yeah, I mean I
Think it should be okay. Thank goodness
I just have to I have to know right away. Yeah, you know
If it was processed and that would be a whole other thing
I don't know because sometimes it gives me the option. I think I think you always can
Like edit it because then it was because it said like it will
Update any monetization stuff on it after you edit it like so I guess you can always edit it
So I can go back to other videos. I guess and
take out some stuff and get them like re monetized or whatever because there's
some videos that are just like you know there's a difference between the ad
revenue and donations and stuff but yeah we all fuck around but we don't want to
fuck with your money dude yeah and if people want to do that then don't come
here man you know they come in here for a fucking other reasons
Yeah, I know. Yeah, so anyone come up come on up on the panel. You're welcome
I'll try to get some energy
But like I was saying I had this weird this weird dream about like, you know ran into M.R. Leviathan at like some um
Some filler center, you know, they'd be skin filler and stuff like and she was having some kind of surgery
Or so and then I was too but it was like everyone was like insane into this place and
And I had this guy with me that kept trying to like steal like the
the anesthesia and painkillers and like get high on everything and I was like
get him out of the room it was a weird dream I dreamt about it was weird I don't
know what happened in the dream but I remember John Stamos was there and
Whitman Mayo remember Whitman Mayo from San Francisco the black dude with the
beard kind of yeah
It's fucked up. I don't know what was going on red foxes. No, no, it's but that's just husband. Okay. Well, here it's just we have coming up here. We have
It's ghost tober ghost what up
Ghosts are you there?
Is the real ghost I think so and nobody else writes crucible
Yeah, I think it's something wrong with his bike, but he has to
Yeah, I'll tire it again. I was like awake
And now I did that and it takes like mental energy to figure out stuff like that for me
And so I got tired again. Oh, yeah, he's gonna come back
You know, that's his online handle for his video game playing to
Play games of them. Yeah, he plays a lot of he does a lot of gaming
That's good. Well ghost everything was saved. It looks like the night was saved
There was another thing like I played another clip that I had to cut out too. It was age-restricted
It was
Beedah's rapping was considered
Vulgar
When Beauty was rapping, it said it was the sexual content policy, because she's like,
I'm gonna fucking, fucking, I don't know, she said the F word a bunch of times.
But, uh, that was that old clip I played, so I had to be careful playing some old clips.
Also, on that, um, that horrible cringe-asaurus, um, bitch, like, um, I got age-restricted for
one of her, when I replayed her rant and everything, and she, and she was like, oh, you, F-A-G-G-O-T,
you're, you've come in your hair and, uh, I don't know why you're, why are you gonna
replay them?
You're giving them clout.
I know, I don't know. I thought it was kind of funny, I mean it was kind of funny. I don't know.
She's just so terrible. She's just so nasty and vicious and evil that I just wanted people to see that.
Yeah, there's a reason.
It's a rumble. Oh my god, I'm so tired. I don't know why I guess where it just like the weather
I did it and I thought that all of a sudden I just felt so tired again. I was like, oh my god
And I just got some sleep
So I'm gonna try to stay out as long as I can
And I'll let ghosts run stuff, but I mean it's like I'll have to let people on and off room
but uh
Yeah, it's just it is kind of stressful to like
you know
I don't like to like talk too much about like my financial situation, but it is kind of like a lot
A lot tighter lately or whatever and and like the YouTube stuff really like really really helps
Me out like once a month whenever that comes through and sometimes it's like, you know
It can I've I've ranged from I think the lowest I ever made on a month since I've been monetized
Was last or is this it's actually this month and it's like a hundred and three dollars or something
I mean, but then like the last
Or this month or last month or the month before or something
It was like over a thousand and so
Well, what adds put ads on your videos some of you know, I do put ads my videos and it's like and the ads are not like
I think I make like 10 bucks or something from all the ads and the shorts and like all that. It's like it's like 10 bucks
It's like really the monies and the memberships and
and the
donations and so
I really and I really do and I do actually and even if my month even if it was like a small month
I think they're super chats and stuff like that that have made up for it, but you know, I'm you know, I
Just I don't want to talk too much about the
the situation, but, you know, I'm really appreciative of people who become members and because the
memberships that I give away, I can give away 10 memberships a month, which I give them away,
but I don't get, I don't get revenue from that. It's just like, it just gives the memberships,
and it's basically, you know, they can renew if they want to, but I don't make revenue from the 10
monthly gifted memberships and so
Put up put up a goal right now put up like one of your goal things
Okay, I'll put a goal on I don't know what I'll go to the 10 people or whatever you do
I'll put up one of those things I'll get I'll get in my speed or something if like they we meet the goal
No, you want you want to make money you don't want to lose money. Oh, that won't that won't be a
yeah because the last time I did the speed I said I'll get in the speedo and like nobody donated
so maybe nobody wants to do it so I don't know what should I do I mean it's like I'll give like
terror readings to everyone in the chat that I mean I'll do that anyway I just don't know
dancing I just don't know like what's going to be a good you know what you know it always gets
people paid I've seen from what I've seen especially the one in Vegas is when people go out on the
I'll do an IRL. I'll do it. I'll do an IRL and especially the Vegas one
They they get fucking like a thousand and I don't I mean I'll go get tacos and everything at the pier
but I
I'll need also like a see now people will say always begging for tacos again. Like I'll need
Probably some actual cash. I'll see how much cash. I don't know. I think I'm gonna be like you know for
Today, I go at the happy hour time or something
But let me see if I can get into this
People love that shit when you go out and you see what's going on. Okay, let's see if I can add a goal
Goal
Okay, I'll do like if I get five super chats
Five dollars or higher in the next three hours
Or tell us a few hours, okay, then I'll do a
IRL at the pier today
What time is it already IRL at pier?
1245 1245, okay. That's there should be plenty of time
Okay, I just put up the goal
Ghosts backstage I think
Okay, goes the backstage. Okay, come on up ghosts
And I might just be like, oh, here's J-Dog.
I might be, hey, J-Dog.
No, what's up, people?
J, what up, man?
Why'd you delete your comments, Sam?
OK, I'm here.
I'm here just to put my avatar on.
Hold on, because I'll be talking,
but I'm not, like, I'm laying down.
So basically, I'll put my avatar up.
How are you?
How are you doing today, psyche?
Are you OK, man?
Yeah, I'm okay. It's just like just stress as soon as I wake up. It's like what was it because of bullshit last night?
The clip yeah the porn bomb. Yeah, dude
Did you get care of it? You good? You took care of it? Yeah. Okay. Thank you ghost. Thank you so much
So Luke's the ghost right there
Already already meeting the already on the way to the goal. So we're gonna help generate some cash
How do I put up my avatar? I forgot and I'm pretty good. I'd see it now. I'm like
For getting how to do everything
Psyche I want to ask you. Did you really see that person in your dream at the at the place Emma? Yeah? Yeah
At first when you were talking about it, I thought you were talking about beta
Then when you said then when you say somebody out, I go this ain't be that that girl when he showed the picture
I'm like no this girl is hottest
Yeah, Emma's hot if she's fucking
She's not that hot bro. Oh, you wouldn't smash her. I mean maybe for like
Are you a straight guy? Okay? Well, I'm not my bad. I said the wrong thing. Are you a straight guy?
Yeah
No, she's hot. She's hot. Look at she has big boobs. She's thin. The catcubes, the dark hair.
I got to see the whole body. I got to see the whole body.
You can pretty much see everything through there. You can pretty much see everything.
Yeah.
You know what it is? It's the nose ring that throws it off for me.
But that could always get taken out. That could always get taken out.
Piercings can always get removed. I don't really like piercings either, but, you know, some things I could look past.
Let me see if I can find a good picture. She's a succubus. Yeah, she's a succubus
Here here's a picture over
Here's a picture over right here
Image file
So psyche what you see she is hot. Yeah
You know what? It's a little too off for me
Not good. Look at the look at the cat to look at the dark clothes
It's her face and the body isn't
She's hot goes what's up goes so looks to go
What's up, dude?
Oh, he did.
Yeah, he almost did.
He almost did that goal.
He was hitting the goal, Psyche, hitting the goal.
Hit the goal.
Did we not meet our goal? I'm asking a question. No, not really did it because I need it has to be like the number of super chats
So it's like any three more super chats $5 or more. Oh
Come on, you can't do
Like you don't even know man, you got a lot of people here that love you
So whenever you're feeling down bro, or you're feeling like depressed or somebody says something back to you always remember man
You got people here that love you and care about you and look forward to you coming on live stream
I want to talk to you and want to hang out with you always remember that bro
Thank you. Let me see. Yeah, you don't gotta thank me man. You just just so you know that you do have people who that love you man. You have them
Stream your let me see. How do I do? No easy. I'm still waiting for that to come
Why is he is he gonna do that? Did he say he was gonna do that?
Do what?
I'm supposed to get yelled at by somebody else
There it is. There's the avatar psyche. Yeah, there we go. Okay. Come on Rudy come on up. Okay. Yeah
I'll be here. I'll be here ghost. I'm gonna cut it with Rudy under the blanket
You're gonna head out to the pier possibly psyche do some IRL. Yeah, I'll go get fish tacos today for that's what's up, bro
Hell, yeah
Yeah, do the IRL people love that shit. Yes, they do man. Dude. I get some IRL. Yes, dude
I got fucking hammered last night. I went to the bars and I got get a troll started calling the bars
They called the bar three different bars. I went to
Yeah, I got Docs and they started calling that ball
Getting kicked out
They thought it was funny. I thought it was funny, too
Well, no, no, they were saying that I needed like penis fungal cream or some shit
I think it's a two more. Let me see. One, two, three. I think it's like, let me see. One, two, three. Oh, yeah. One, two, three, four. Okay, there's two at a time.
All right. I did. I did three more, by the way. 20 bucks. That doesn't count. I'm just gonna, like, give me a try. I'm a dirty fucking bastard.
You did the whole goal?
I don't know, is that how I do it?
How much more do I want to get?
That's awesome that you're doing it, Ghost.
Well, let somebody else do it.
Oh, Christine.
Oh, OK.
Thank you ghost, I appreciate you and I'll go
Yeah, it's ghost panel today ghost panel ghost ghost is our our hero was donated last night a lot
Donated today don't talk dumb dumb
This is cool spot. Hell yeah
Let me donate you you know, hold on hold on my wife is dropping
Let me talk to God if you guys don't mind. I'm right here. Yeah, what up?
God what up?
My wife I was fucked up my bad
What are you here dumb fuck? All right, I'm here
No, no, no cuz you did you did me dirty last night. Oh, I'm gonna say gonna leave. I'm just gonna leave
I'm just gonna leave stop fucking leaving
No, you did that shit like four or five times
You did that shit a lot Godie do you know Godie you were here
How many times Godie three four times before yeah at least four I agree. Okay. Well the important thing is he's here now
That's that's what we got
I
Let me run one with psych I'm tired of your shit you personally
Yeah, I'm talking to you brother. Yeah, I'm talking to you
Look at the blanket. I can't think of the abuse this morning. I don't give a fuck about another don't fucking ask
Ask for money and when someone actually donates that shit and you act like a bitch
Straight up. If you're calling you insulted page so page left. I'm in the salt
Well, okay, that's a good well that's
That's a claim
You said fuck the cards. I don't want to see those fucking cards. I didn't say that I never want
Page rage quick. It was supposed to I don't give a fuck what page said
What you get kicked off my own fucking panel is gonna give you a beautiful reading you said fuck
I paid all that money to what it's supposed to be it goes
I have relationships maintained too and so I don't give a fuck. It was a ghost panel
They don't understand he's
Years one night
Ghost ran the panel because he paid all that money this fucking I gave all the money respect me
That's one one how much money the page gift how much money the ghosts get
Let's compare the two
Page gave over self
Because I fucking was like how many hundreds of dollars
Yeah, I mean I did multiple multiple multiple last night was about a hundred
Yeah, oh last night. I bought a hundred, but uh, I gave her how many times
But what 20 you have a lot of you have a lot of
You have a lot of credit
I'm gonna say can you like at least fuck it on and like not like chase like friends away
Well already mad at me kind of to go to panel
I don't know your friends your friends are your friends like they understand
No, they don't understand. No, they don't understand you
Yeah, ghost can ghost can do whatever he wants right now if he wants to
Now that's fucked up so I can you know that shit
What do you then do you like you to seem like be a piece of shit like you always do where you're gonna do make a AI song about me
What you should we actually know each other's like
Who the fuck else is donating me
Yeah, nobody you promise you promise it and you don't do it. You don't fulfill
Who is that I don't know oh, that's easy easy what up, man, I can't see it so small
Yo
What up? What up? What up? What up motherfuckers? My name is ghost and since like he's not saying nothing to me
I'm gonna cry about stuff
Okay, so much on yesterday. We should focus on today's case. I think he's gonna do IRL right in a little while to go get fish
I tuned in, you know God was here then this guy came up and you came up and I just came up
So I just I don't know what's going on, but we're just thinking going IRL. I'm taking off in five minutes
That was like he says he's gonna get fish tacos. No
Oh, yeah, so he's walking down a pier in his Speedos is about to go down
I think psyche you're gonna go in your sick clothes right psyche you're gonna go in or you know dressed yeah
Go with the priest with the white hair
Yeah, take the wig
Oh the way yeah
With the way with the breeze I'm telling you gonna kill it like you're gonna kill it with psyche. I forgot about the
Somebody else. I need some more donations. I want to get more donations. Okay. We gotta get more. We just sent you $15
That was for the first one and we got to do it for another another goal. Yeah, you want to get a male prostitute
Oh somebody's you know, you want somebody to order you a male prostitute we just sent well
Well, well whoever psyche special delivery guy, I already know he wants okay, what's a male prostitute
Prepaid by the world pre-paid you want to lose booty psyche you want to lose booty or tight booty?
I want I want like a hot like straight acting straight looking guy, but just I mean thank you
Are you a topper bottom?
Okay, okay
He's gonna want he just described everything how J dog look. I'm so sorry J dogs. Yeah, I'm a J dog
Okay
I
We are gonna meet up with you psyche. I don't live that far from you. I am gonna meet up with you, bro
We're gonna do some IRL. We're gonna get some fish tacos. We're gonna get drunk. We're gonna get hammered
Um, dude, I want to get some DMT, you know, we get some good DMT
You can make it even better
Cool
Yeah, there's um, oh yeah, I actually have a friend that she has like these pens
I don't know if she has I can get so get one, but is it like a vape pen? Is it like this?
Okay, yeah, hell yeah
I like I would get so fucking high on it, but uh, yeah, but I think yeah, they got
Would you be everything?
They dog and we're gonna go and get we're gonna go ham. We're gonna go go crazy, bro. We're gonna get drunk
Yeah, I'm in Kelly. I'm only like a few hours away from psyche. I'm not that far from my friend just told me weed soda
They got weed soda out there. Yeah, they got weed. Oh psyche. You want some lean?
Do you like lean psyche? No, not lean weed soda. I got lean is
Lean is something else
Yeah, I like me. I love me. Yeah
But yeah, we have weak soda out here and we got all kinds of things with weed in it
We got weed lotion, bro. Like lotion you put on your body. It's got weed in it. I have a machine
It's called like the it's called like magic butter or something like that
I can you just basically put a bunch of weed in it and like there's some melted butter and then it's like you
You turn it off for like or actually it melts the butter. It's like it's got a big bat
It heats it and then it's like you can make lotions with it
You can make the butter and you just pour it out into the molds and stuff like that
I was cooking with it and like getting
Everything that goes back
Because the fumes are
Real quick before I go who the fuck just kicked me out
I didn't nobody
Nobody kicked you out you got bad service
Pay us a pair of psyche like you could be on in at least like you did not kick you out. He just said it
You just gave the man a hundred almost a hundred dollars like why would you kick you out after that? Come on?
That make no sense your service
Now, service didn't drop, it was blocked.
All of a sudden, I'm blocked.
Listen, I give more money to everybody
It's not about that
If you're a good supporter and you just giving him money not to buy him out just to support him for whatever reason
You most like you look like you're buying them out for airtime my dude, so I'm just saying
You should come prove what you're being up here. I'm just a panel privilege
Nigga this ain't your house. This ain't your house. This ain't your kingdom. The fuck is wrong with me?
Block nigga. I don't give a fuck. How much money you send so what nigga suck a dick it down
Yeah, I don't give a fuck you say one more word. I'm gonna put you on a t-shirt
Put me on the t-shirt bitch. Put me in the back. Put me in a t-shirt. Pay for it